Guide to the Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records, ca. 1960-1989
Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records,
- Series I. Assignments
  - March 1970
    - Concrete stress lab, 7032 (Box 14)
    - New Campus store, interior, 7033 (Box 14)
    - Mobile Radio/Telescope, 7034 (Box 14)
    - Referendum and Patrick the dog, 7035 (Box 14)
    - Heptagonals 1970, 7036 (Box 14)
    - Hockey, R1-2, 7037 (Box 14)
    - Solar Eclipse, 7038 (Box 14)
    - Small Items sale at Willard Straight, 7039 (Box 14)
    - Metallic Hydrogen, Engineering, 70310 (Box 14)
    - Donald Eddy, Rare Books librarian, 70311 (Box 14)
    - Apples, 70312 (Box 14)
    - Bird cages, Architecture, 70313 (Box 14)
    - Carl Sagan, Professor (pre-Cosmos, 70314 (Box 14)
    - Women's Liberation demonstration on the Pill, Willard Straight and Day Hall boardroom, 70315 (Box 14)
    - Annual Green Dragon Parade, 70316 (Box 14)
    - Fire outside of Day Hall; Construction and model of Cornell, 70317 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Trustees press conference, 70318 (Box 14)
    - Turner, 70319 (Box 14)
    - Shack on 'old Rusty' site, 70320 (Box 14)
    - Edwin Salpeter, Nuclear Physics, 70321 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Hockey, 70322 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Hockey - NCAA, 70323 (Box 14)
  - April 1970
    - Cornell crew, 7041 (Box 14)
    - Wordsworth, 7042 (Box 14)
    - Dale Corson, Rotary, 7043 (Box 14)
    - Arthur Goldberg, US rep to the U.N., 7044 (Box 14)
    - Campus Store, interior, 7045 (Box 14)
    - Elm trees burning in gorge, 7046 (Box 14)
    - Moon dust; Professor Morrison, metal welding sculpture, 7047 (Box 14)
    - Fire and crisis at Africana Studies Center, 7048 (Box 14)
    - New York Convocation, 7049 (Box 14)
    - Tribute to Daniel Berrigan - 'America is hard to find' weekend, 70410 (Box 14)
    - Astronaut O'Leary; Heppell, Bio Chemistry; Wallace; Steven W. Jacobs, Architecture, 70411 (Box 14)
    - Hotel Ezra Cornell, 70412 (Box 14)
    - Glass spots, safety spots, 70413 (Box 14)
    - Student and computer, 70414 (Box 14)
  - May 1970
    - Art class model, 7051 (Box 14)
    - Student Strike and road blocks; Ben Nichols; students swimming in gorge; Harry Parker, 7052 (Box 14)
    - B & P A school, 7053 (Box 14)
    - Cornell lacrosse, 7054 (Box 14)
    - Edgar Whiting, manager of Willard Straight, 7055 (Box 14)
    - Spring campus scenes; professor Abrams, Walter LaFever, widelux views, 7056 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Plantations, 7057 (Box 14)
    - Professor Peggy Lawler, 7058 (Box 14)
    - Eldon Kenworthy, 7059 (Box 14)
    - Delridge Hunter, COSEP head, 70510 (Box 14)
    - Nitza Schmidt, University female chimes master, 70511 (Box 14)
    - Electric car, 70512 (Box 14)
    - Llenroc Delta Phi fraternity house, 70513 (Box 14)
    - Plant sale, 70514 (Box 14)
    - Senate Executive Committee, individuals, 70515 (Box 14)
    - Professor Randel, 70516 (Box 14)
    - Professor Harold E. Samuel, Music, 70517 (Box 14)
    - Professor Robert Palmer, 70518 (Box 14)
    - Infra-red scenes, 70519 (Box 14)
    - Paper furniture, 70520 (Box 14)
  - June 1970
    - Professor Henn, 7061 (Box 14)
    - Professor Warren, Law School, 7062 (Box 14)
    - Dale Corson with cap and gown, 7063 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Administrators; G. McFarren, CUAA; etc., 7064 (Box 14)
    - McManus, 7065 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Commencement '70, 7066 (Box 14)
    - Dale Corson in color, 7067 (Box 14)
    - Alumni Reunion '70, 7068 (Box 14)
    - More Cornell Commencement '70 (R22-Corson investiture, black student, Willard Straight, 7069 (Box 14)
    - Cornell crew vs Penn, 70610 (Box 14)
    - Steve Goodwin, 70611 (Box 14)
    - Welcome Alumni, 70612 (Box 14)
    - Dr. Robert Capranica, 70613 (Box 14)
    - Retiring employees, 70614 (Box 14)
    - Creek diversion, 70615 (Box 14)
  - July 1970
    - Experiment in Cryogenics, 7076 (Box 14)
    - Committee, 7077; R1, R3 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Regional, 7078 (Box 14)
    - Catherine Fabricant, Microbiologist, 7079 (Box 14)
    - 600mm Lens Test, 70710 (Box 14)
    - 39th Annual Golf Association Junior Championship, 70711 (Box 14)
  - August 1970
    - Auto Accident, 7081 (Box 14)
    - People on hill, 7084 (Box 14)
    - Gathering on Arts Quad, 7085 (Box 14)
    - Fencing Practice, 7087 (Box 14)
    - Panoramic View of Cornell, 70811 (Box 14)
    - Sundial, 70812 (Box 14)
    - Traffic Control, Steel Construction, Football Practice, 70813; R1-R3C (Box 14)
    - Captain Jackson, Naval ROTC, R1 * David Wyatt, R2 * Paul Dean, R3, 70814 (Box 14)
    - Lawn over Campus Store; Wee Stinky Glen, 70815 (Box 14)
    - Infra-red Telephoto, 70816 (Box 14)
    - Women's Liberation Demonstration; Professor Feldman, 70817 (Box 14)
  - September 1970
    - Tom Tobin, Coordinator of New York State Relations, 7091 (Box 14)
    - Ground Breaking for Johnson Museum, 7092 (Box 14)
    - Freshman Arrival, R1 & 2, 7093 (Box 14)
    - Sage Chapel, interior, 7094 (Box 14)
    - University Ombudsmen: Hart, Spano, Cook, Sapakie, 7095 (Box 14)
    - Building construction, elms and specimens, 7096 (Box 14)
    - Kappa Delta, R1 * Credit Cards, R2, 7097 (Box 14)
    - Parents' Convocation, 7098 (Box 14)
    - Freshman Registration, R1-3, 7099 (Box 14)
    - Freshman Convocation, R1-3, 70910 (Box 14)
    - Parents Reception, 70911 (Box 14)
    - Registration, R1 & 2, 70912 (Box 14)
    - University Senate in Kauffman Auditorium, R1 & 2, 70913 (Box 14)
    - Campus Store; Willard Straight tree stump, R1 & 2, 70914 (Box 14)
    - Alternate bookstore at Willard Straight, 70915 (Box 14)
    - Hawks (for Ralph K, 70916 (Box 14)
    - Dog (for Ralph K, 70917 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 70918 (Box 14)
    - Evelyn Addams cookbook, 70919 (Box 14)
    - Activities fair at Willard Straight, R1 & 2, 70920 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes and Chizuo Kato, 70921 (Box 14)
    - Sage House, 70922 (Box 14)
    - Barnes Hall, interior and exterior, 70923 (Box 14)
    - Radio telescope in Danby, 70924 (Box 14)
    - New Cosep office in barnes Hall, 70925 (Box 14)
    - New sculpture behind A.D.White Museum, 70926 (Box 14)
    - United Fund Drive, 70927 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 70928 (Box 14)
    - Professor Moore, Dean, I & L R, 70929 (Box 14)
    - Professor Risley, Assistant Dean, I & L R, 70930 (Box 14)
    - Law Library, R1 & 2, 70931 (Box 14)
    - Model of Animal Research building, 70932 (Box 14)
    - Infra-red food heater in Martha Van, 70933 (Box 14)
    - LaVerne Rolle, '74, 70934 (Box 14)
    - Biology and Society lecture (not V.S. negs, 70935 (Box 14)
  - October 1970
    - Campus scenes, 70101 (Box 14)
    - Frederic W. Scott, 70102 (Box 14)
    - Cornell vs Lehigh, football (10-3-70, 70103 (Box 14)
    - New Risley dining room, 70104 (Box 14)
    - The 'Pick-up' (Balch store, 70105 (Box 14)
    - Chained typewriter, 70106 (Box 14)
    - Traffic booths, 70107 (Box 14)
    - Construction progress, 70108 (Box 14)
    - Robert Plane, University Provost, 70109 (Box 14)
    - Archives copies, 701010 (Box 14)
    - Donald F. Berth, Engineering Administration, 701011 (Box 14)
    - Football, Cornell vs Penn (10-10-70) R1 & 2 (RH) R3 (Chee, 701012 (Box 14)
    - Fall campus scenes, 701013 (Box 14)
    - Lightweight football, 701014 (Box 14)
    - Mark Barlow, Vice Provost, 701015 (Box 14)
    - Football, Cornell vs Penn, R1-3 D. Chee, 701016 (Box 14)
    - Uris Hall (Social Sciences) building program, 701017 (Box 14)
    - 25th Anniversary, I & L R School, 701018 (Box 14)
    - 150 football, Cornell vs Penn, 701019 (Box 14)
    - Nicholas Noyes, 701020 (Box 14)
    - Football, Cornell vs Yale, R1, R2, R4 (RH), R3 (SG, 701021 (Box 14)
    - Football fans, 701022 (Box 14)
    - Recess, 701023 (Box 14)
    - Test roll on Konica C5, 701024 (Box 14)
    - New barn, 701025 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Council luncheon, 701026 (Box 14)
    - Tailgating, 701027 (Box 14)
    - Huff-Death families, 701028 (Box 14)
    - Excavation, Johnson Art Museum, 701029 (Box 14)
  - November 1970
    - Campus scenes from McGraw Tower, R1-5, 70111A (Box 14)
    - Swan at Stewart Park, 70112A (Box 14)
    - I & L R School 25th anniversary banquet, R1-5 (SG, 70113A (Box 14)
    - "Black Images", 70114A (Box 14)
    - Dorm T-shirts, 70115A (Box 14)
    - Hockey ticket line, 70116A (Box 14)
    - Library Tower at night, 70117A (Box 14)
    - Dogs, 70118A (Box 14)
    - Bird planetarium, Professor Stephen T. Emlen, 70119A (Box 14)
    - Golf classes, 701110A (Box 14)
    - Moot Court winners, 701111A (Box 14)
    - Dorm 8, International living unit, 701112A (Box 14)
    - Herb Williams dedication, 701113A (Box 14)
    - Campus store, interior and exterior, 701114A (Box 14)
    - Homecoming, '70, 701115A (Box 14)
    - Turkey chase, feature, 701116A (Box 14)
    - Football, Cornell vs Dartmouth, R1-5, 701117A (Box 14)
    - Frozen books, 701118A (Box 14)
    - Uris Hall building construction, 701119A (Box 14)
    - Professor Fernando Noronha, 701120A (Box 14)
    - Glider in front of Willard Straight, 701121A (Box 14)
    - Cecelie Dexter, pool shark, 701122A (Box 14)
  - December 1970
    - Underpass, Plantations Drive, 70121A (Box 14)
    - Fall Creek bridge to Forest Home Drive, 70122A (Box 14)
    - Hockey '70 (R. Shew, 70123A (Box 14)
    - Allan J. Mayer, 70124A (Box 14)
    - Play preparations, R1-3, 70125A (Box 14)
    - Christmas 'balls', tree decoration, 70126A (Box 14)
    - Trees, 70127A (Box 14)
    - Sage Chapel Christmas concert, 70128A (Box 14)
    - Trees with light 'stars', Olin, trees, tower, 70129A (Box 14)
    - Professor Clyde Boyer, 701210A (Box 14)
    - Snow scenes from Library tower, 701211A (Box 14)
    - Cornell food truck, 701212A (Box 14)
    - Bell ringing for Vietnam War Dead, 701213A (Box 14)
    - Snow scenes, R1-3, 701214A (Box 14)
    - G. Michael McHugh, 701215A (Box 14)
    - Lab of Plasma Studies, 701216A (Box 14)
    - Last landing of the "Far Above", 701217A (Box 14)
    - Douglas Dowd, Professor, protester, 701218A (Box 14)
  - January 1971
    - ILR assignment, 7110 (Box 14)
    - New Dean of Students offices in Barnes Hall, 7111 (Box 14)
    - OPI Audio Center (Lincoln Hall, 7112 (Box 14)
    - Africana Center, R1-5, 7113 (Box 14)
    - Professor William Keeton in pigeon loft, 7114 (Box 14)
    - Professor Gustavus H. robinson, Law School Emeritus, 7115 (Box 14)
    - Statue of Ezra Cornell, 7116 (Box 14)
    - Plasma physics: Mike Ury and Professor Rostoker, 7117 (Box 14)
    - Final exams '71, 7118 (Box 14)
    - Phil Ritson, 7119 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 71110 (Box 14)
    - Hockey, Cornell vs Harvard, 71111 (Box 14)
    - Paying tuition, 71112 (Box 14)
    - Thingamajigs and dog (Bugger, 71113 (Box 14)
    - Untitled, 71114 (Box 14)
  - February 1971
    - Administrators: Robert Miller, Lyle Carter, Arthur Peterson, Steve Miller, Jackson Hall, Paul McKeegan, Ralph Koskey, Lowell George, Tom Tobin, Diedrick Willers, Tom Mackesey, Lew Durland, John Anderson, Harry Kisken, Byron Yaffe, 7120
      - Contact sheet (Box 14)
    - Registration, 7122 (Box 14)
    - The 'Galloping Gourmet', Graham Kerr, 7123 (Box 14)
    - Electronic Flea Market, 7124 (Box 14)
    - Spinal prosthetic, Dr. Timothy Brasmer, 7125 (Box 14)
    - Alumni Hockey, R1-3, 7126 (Box 14)
    - Musicians, 7127 (Box 14)
    - Teal, new bird, 7128 (Box 14)
    - Synchrotron Computer, 7129 (Box 14)
    - Day Care Center, 71210 (Box 14)
    - Dog prosthetic, 71211 (Box 14)
    - Snow scenes, 71212 (Box 14)
    - Black studies professors, 71213 (Box 14)
    - Law students at Auburn prison, 71214 (Box 14)
    - Physics teaching aid, Professor Littauer, 71215 (Box 14)
    - New offices in barnes Hall, 71216 (Box 14)
    - Guest Chef, 71217 (Box 14)
    - Senate voting, 71218 (Box 14)
    - Regional history, 71219 (Box 14)
    - Grank Mayo retirement party, 71220 (Box 14)
    - Ed Marinaro award, 71221 (Box 14)
    - Hockey, Corness vs St. Lawrence, 71222 (Box 14)
    - Training a campus cop, R1-5, 71223 (Box 14)
    - Stimson stuff, 71224 (Box 14)
    - Student trustees: Gordon Chand, Louise Shelley, 71225 (Box 14)
    - Professor Hudson with desert squirrel, 71226 (Box 14)
    - Computer at Stimson, 71227 (Box 14)
    - Russian Art exhibit, 71228 (Box 14)
    - University Senate, 71229 (Box 14)
    - Marinaro in color, 71230 (Box 14)
    - Professor Walter Lynn and epidemic stimulator, 71231 (Box 14)
    - New Student Trustees: Robert C. Gottlieb and Stephanie Seremetis, 71232 (Box 14)
    - Ed Marinaro, 71233 (Box 14)
  - March 1971
    - Dr. Wimsatt and bats, 7131 (Box 14)
    - Women's basketball, 7132 (Box 14)
    - COSEP honors dinner, 7133 (Box 14)
    - Heptagonals, '71, R1-5, 7134 (Box 14)
    - Hotel Administration project, 7135 (Box 14)
    - New Trustee, Desdemona Jacobs, 7136 (Box 14)
    - Snow scenes, 7137 (Box 14)
    - Cornell hockey, 7138 (Box 14)
    - Dog lab at James A. Baker Institute, 7139 (Box 14)
    - Senate Executive Committee, 71310 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 71311 (Box 14)
    - Seymour Smidt, 71312 (Box 14)
    - Reactor stress test, 71313 (Box 14)
    - Gene Likens, water test, 71314 (Box 14)
    - Cornell crew, 71315 (Box 14)
    - Diver, Larry More, 71316 (Box 14)
    - Arson at Barton Hall, 71317 (Box 14)
    - Saunders Redding, 71318 (Box 14)
    - St. Patrick's Day, R1-4, 71319 (Box 14)
    - Whitney Young memorial, color, 71320 (Box 14)
    - Faculty Council of representatives meeting, 71321 (Box 14)
    - Complaint box, 71322 (Box 14)
    - Professor Lee Miller, plants, 71323 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Alumni University, Allentown, PA, R1-4, 71324 (Box 14)
  - April 1971
    - Marge Edsall, 7141 (Box 14)
    - Professor John Wells, 7142 (Box 14)
    - Janice D. Willis, 7143 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 7144 (Box 14)
    - Social Sciences building picket, 7145 (Box 14)
    - WVBR, 7146 (Box 14)
    - McGraw interiors, 7147 (Box 14)
    - Dale Corson's birthday cake, 7148 (Box 14)
    - Professor and Mrs. Ernst Gombrich, 7149 (Box 14)
    - Pots and pans sale, 71410 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 71411 (Box 14)
    - Kermit C. Parsons, 71412 (Box 14)
    - "To All Things Black and Beautiful", 71413 (Box 14)
    - Reception for Morris Bishop, 71414 (Box 14)
    - Book awards, 71415 (Box 14)
    - HAP demonstration, 71416 (Box 14)
    - Cornell crew, 71417 (Box 14)
    - Composers, 71418 (Box 14)
    - Electronic music, 71419 (Box 14)
    - Blue bus, 71420 (Box 14)
    - Jordani Society small animal sale, 71421 (Box 14)
    - Anything That Floats but a Boat" race, 71422 (Box 14)
    - Geodesic dome on Quad, 71423 (Box 14)
  - May 1971
    - Clark Hall, extensive coverage, R1-31, 7151 (Box 14)
    - "To All Things Black and Beautiful", W. Tree for WCNY, 7153 (Box 14)
    - Exam book, 7152 (Box 14)
    - Baby hawk, 7155 (Box 14)
    - Harke rally, 7156 (Box 14)
    - Professor Hudson, 7157 (Box 14)
    - Sam Woodside, 7158 (Box 14)
    - Arts Quad, 7159 (Box 14)
    - Mobe paints pavillion, 71510 (Box 14)
    - Professor Maas, sleep and dreams, 71511 (Box 14)
    - Ithakords, 71512 (Box 14)
    - "To All Things Black and Beautiful", 71513 (Box 14)
    - Tower Club, R1-4, 71514 (Box 14)
    - YMCA Day Care center, 71515 (Box 14)
    - Female Engineering students, 71516 (Box 14)
    - George Healey's apple, 71517 (Box 14)
    - Cornell lacrosse, 71518 (Box 14)
    - Japanese students association, 71519 (Box 14)
    - Medieval Fair at Risley, R1-3, 71520 (Box 14)
    - Professor William Gurowitz, 71521 (Box 14)
  - June 1971
    - Cornell lacrosse, R1-3, 7161 (Box 14)
    - Radiation Lab computer, 7162 (Box 14)
    - Scanning electron microscope, 7163 (Box 14)
    - Johnson Museum model and Archives copy, 7164 (Box 14)
    - Malcolm X memorial, 7165 (Box 14)
    - Widelux from tower and new chimes mechanism, 7166 (Box 14)
    - 21mm from tower, 7167 (Box 14)
    - Beebe Lake drained, 7168 (Box 14)
    - Pleasant Grove and Hasbrouck apts, 7169 (Box 14)
  - July 1971
    - Schoellkopf and rescue attempt, 7170 (Box 14)
    - ROTC Commissioning, 7171 (Box 14)
    - Commencement, '71, R1-8, 7172 (Box 14)
    - Cornell lacrosse, (L. Baum) R1-3, 7173 (Box 14)
    - Press conference, Purcell and Gottlieb, 7174 (Box 14)
    - Alumni Reunion, R1-25, 7175 (Box 14)
    - Joe Frost retirement, 7171X (Box 14)
    - Professor Archie Ammons, 7172X (Box 14)
    - Wheel locking device, 'Denver Boot', 7173X (Box 14)
    - Baby hawk, 7174X (Box 14)
    - Blanchard Rideout, 7175X (Box 14)
    - Infra-red, 7176 (Box 14)
    - Cornell pottery made by Elijah Cornell, 7177 (Box 14)
    - Kunken fund, 7178 (Box 14)
    - Junior hockey, 7179 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Dairy bar, 71710 (Box 14)
    - Nursery at Commons, 71711 (Box 14)
    - Model Cities group, 71712 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Alumni University, 71713 (Box 14)
    - Polyturf, color, 71714 (Box 14)
    - Polyturf, R1-3, 71715 (Box 14)
    - Michael Gill, Law Library, 71716 (Box 14)
    - Sports Fitness school with Pete Carhart, 71717 (Box 14)
  - September 1971
    - Football practice on polyturf, 7191 (Box 14)
    - Sapsucker Pond drained, 7192 (Box 14)
    - Howard C. Kramer, Assistant Dean of Students, 7193 (Box 14)
    - Freshman arrival, 7194 (Box 14)
    - Registration, 7195 (Box 14)
    - Arts Quad fair, 7196 (Box 14)
    - Tuition payment, 7197 (Box 14)
    - Opening of North Campus Commons, 7198 (Box 14)
    - Dale Corson tours North Campus Commons, 7199 (Box 14)
    - Microlab, Relaxation exercises, 71910 (Box 14)
    - Rites of Passage', 71911 (Box 14)
    - North Campus Commons, 71912 (Box 14)
    - Attica protest, 71913 (Box 14)
    - Wild Animals, Vet School, 71914 (Box 14)
    - International students and host families, 71915 (Box 14)
    - Halloween, 71916 (Box 14)
    - Transfer students in Engineering, 71917 (Box 14)
    - Students in line for Financial Aid, 71918 (Box 14)
    - Cornell vs U. of Mass, scrimmage, 71919 (Box 14)
    - Attica Memorial March, 71920 (Box 14)
    - North Campus area, 71921 (Box 14)
    - Ben Perez, Engineering scholarship winner, 71922 (Box 14)
    - Parallel parking, Tower Road, 71923 (Box 14)
    - Repairing Barton and Ives steps, 71924 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 71925 (Box 14)
    - Parachute jump, R1-3, 71926 (Box 14)
    - Snakes at Stimson, 71927 (Box 14)
    - Crowded micro-biology lab, 71928 (Box 14)
    - Car bumper sculpture by Jason Seley, 71929 (Box 14)
    - Professor David Grossvogel, 71930 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 71931 (Box 14)
    - Professor Peakall and ringnecked dove, 71932 (Box 14)
    - Football, Cornell vs Colgate, 71933 (Box 14)
    - Kids reading Chronicle, 71934 (Box 14)
    - Professor M. H. Abrams, 71935 (Box 14)
  - October 1971
    - Chained bicycles, 71101 (Box 14)
    - ACUSNY Presidents, 71102 (Box 14)
    - Cholesterol: butter and eggs, 71103 (Box 14)
    - Under the dome at Sibley, 71104 (Box 14)
    - Campus store annual sale, 71105 (Box 14)
    - Jordani Club sale, 71106 (Box 14)
    - United Fund, 71107 (Box 14)
    - Computer in Sociology, 71108 (Box 14)
    - Mr. Clark, 71109 (Box 14)
    - Soccer, Cornell vs Princeton, 711010 (Box 14)
    - Problems of the city, discussion, 711011 (Box 14)
    - Football, Cornell vs Princeton, R1-3, 711012 (Box 14)
    - Dean Cooke, campus scenes, 711013 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes from belltower with 600mm lens, 711014 (Box 14)
    - Containment facility at Mitchell St. lab, 711015 (Box 14)
    - Engineering students with model cars, 711016 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Trustees meeting, R1-3, 711017 (Box 14)
    - Trustees with students, 711018 (Box 14)
    - Fall-In at Cornell Plantations, 711019 (Box 14)
    - Cornell Apple orchard, 711020 (Box 14)
    - Archives pictures of Engineering Quad, 711021 (Box 14)
    - Engineering Convocation, R1-5, 711022 (Box 14)
    - Cyrus Eaton visits Cornell, 711023 (Box 14)
    - Jackie Mangum, soil judging champ, 711024 (Box 14)
  - November 1971
    - Cross country meet, 71111A (Box 14)
    - Garage on Route 366, 71112A (Box 14)
    - Aaron Copland, 71113A (Box 14)
    - Math students, 71114A (Box 14)
    - Fuertes exhibit at Olin, 71115A (Box 14)
    - Football, Cornell vs Columbia, R1-9, 71116A (Box 14)
    - Ramon Rivera, 71117A (Box 14)
    - Hockey ticket line, 71118A (Box 14)
    - Sherlock Holmes fan, 71119A (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 711110A (Box 14)
    - Mann Library, 711111A (Box 14)
    - Martha Van Rensslaer, 711112A (Box 14)
    - Dining facilities, R1-3, 711113A (Box 14)
    - Cornell hockey, (R. Shew, 711114A (Box 14)
    - Women's hockey, 711115A (Box 14)
    - Ardella Blanford, Pat Arthur, Personnel, 711116A (Box 14)
    - Undergraduate teaching assistants, 711117A (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 711118A (Box 14)
    - National Science Foundation project, 711119A (Box 14)
  - December 1971
    - Michael Kammen, Professor, 71121A (Box 14)
    - W. Wolfgang Holdheim, 71122A (Box 14)
    - Architecture display at A. D. White Museum, 71123A (Box 14)
    - Milton S. Gould, 71124A (Box 14)
    - Booking at the Straight, 71125A (Box 14)
    - Cornell hockey, (R. Shew, 71126A (Box 14)
    - Christmas trees, 71127A (Box 14)
    - Glass crushing, 71128A (Box 14)
    - Baking cookies at Ecology house, 71129A (Box 14)
    - Birdfeeder at Ornithology Lab, 711210A (Box 14)
    - European Hotel School students award to Ed Marinaro, 711211A (Box 14)
    - Corson press conference, 11-23-71, 711212A (Box 14)
    - Dr. Allyn B. Ley, Gannett Clinic, 711213A (Box 14)
    - Ecology house sign, 711214A (Box 14)
  - January 1972
    - James Tate's dog, 7211 (Box 14)
    - Sapsucker pond filled, 7212 (Box 14)
    - Professor Kenneth Torrance, 7213 (Box 14)
    - Straight Ivy Room, 7214 (Box 14)
    - Danby Dish, Radio/Telescope, 7215 (Box 14)
    - Savage animal lab, 7216 (Box 14)
    - Uris Library, A.D.White Reading room, 7217 (Box 14)
    - Women's hockey team, 7218 (Box 14)
    - Registration, 7219 (Box 14)
    - Professor Charles Wilcox, 72110 (Box 14)
    - Professor Lauriston Sharp, 72111 (Box 14)
    - Campus scenes, 72112 (Box 14)
    - Sapsucker woods snow, 72113 (Box 14)
    - HAP Storefront, Human Assistance Program, 72114 (Box 14)
    - Glee Club Far East tour, R1-8, (J. NichoLls, 72115 (Box 14)
  - February 1972
    - Presidential press conference, 7221 (Box 14)
    - Traffic booth, 7222 (Box 14)
    - Center for Urban Development (old Alpha Chi Rho house, 7223 (Box 14)
    - Sage Career Center, 7224 (Box 14)
    - Ducks in Wee Stinky Glen, 7225 (Box 14)
    - Bird at Ornithology: Tinamou, 7226 (Box 14)
    - Llurhos Civilization exhibit, 7227 (Box 14)
    - Baseball practice at Bacon Cage, 7228 (Box 14)
    - Student Sculpture, 7229 (Box 14)
    - Professors Rossi and Thoron with Law student Karen Johnson, 72210 (Box 14)
    - Dick Bertrand and hockey co-captains, 72211 (Box 14)
    - Demonstration against Honeywell, 72212 (Box 14)
    - Rare book, 72213 (Box 14)
    - Snow scenes, 72214 (Box 14)
    - Robert Platt, new student Trustee, 72215 (Box 14)
    - CAL demonstration, 72216 (Box 14)
    - University Halls #3, 72217 (Box 14)
    - The BIG snow storm, 72218 (Box 14)
    - Jack Warner and track team (B. Smith, 72219 (Box 14)
    - Demonstration against Sylvania, etc., recruiters, 72220 (Box 14)
  - March 1972
    - Heptagonals, R1-4, 7231 (Box 14)
    - Gail Povar, student advisors, 7232 (Box 14)
    - Weight lifter, Nick Weingarten '73, 7233 (Box 14)
    - Auburn Prison Art exhibit, 7235 (Box 14)
    - Senate voting, 7236 (Box 14)
    - Cornell hockey, (R. Shew, 7237 (Box 14)
    - Steve Adams, student working steam table in North Campus dining, 7238 (Box 14)
    - Senate ballot counting and gavel transfer, 7239 (Box 14)
    - Janine Jamieson and Roger Dube, American Indian students, 72310 (Box 14)
    - Arthur Ruoff, new teaching methods, 72311 (Box 14)
    - Women's Art Festival, 72312 (Box 14)
    - Cornell hockey, Cornell vs. Providence, R1-5, 72313 (Box 14)
    - New student Trustee, Bruce Stone, 72314 (Box 14)